《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
我一直对摄影感兴趣
Photography was always my passion.
我就想  那我为什么不做摄影工作呢
I figured, why not make it my job?
这些照片拍得很好
These are great.
冰霜  你总是陪着我
Frost, you have always been there for me.
我从没想过
It never occurred to me
你想要过自己的生活
that you might want to live a life.
和你做生意很愉快
Nice doing business with you.
瑞秋·罗素
挚爱的母亲
这是潜在的治疗方法
This is a potential cure.
粘合剂是什么
What's the bonding agent?
暗物质
Dark matter.
尖端科研实验室有我进行下一步
S.T.A.R. Labs has the dark matter
需要的暗物质
I need to take the next step.
我的药物有用
My cure will work.
或违背他们的意愿把他们变成了超能力者
Or turn them into meta-humans against their will.
你无法避免眼前的危机
You cannot avoid the coming crisis.
只管告诉我怎么做
Just tell me what I can do.
闪电侠必须死
The Flash must die.
我盯着那张报纸看了好多年
I stared at that newspaper for so many years.
《中城市民》报
闪电侠消失于危机之中
"Flash Missing, Vanishes in Crisis."
2024年4月25日
起初它就像是一个引导
First it felt like a guide.
证明事情正在向正确的方向发展
You know, like proof that things were headed in the right direction.
朱莉·格瑞尔
然后它就变成了悬在我头顶的一把剑
Then it became a sword hanging over my head.
我有时感觉
A part of me always felt like...
25年后  闪电侠仍未出现
若我在即将到来的危机中消失了
if I vanish in whatever crisis is coming...
也许我仍然活在某个地方
maybe I was still out there somewhere,
在想办法回到你们身边
looking for a way to come back to you.
但根据监视者所说  那不会发生
According to The Monitor, that doesn't happen.
"要拯救亿万人的生命
"To save the lives of billions,
闪电侠就必须死"
the Flash must die."
这是什么屁话
What kind crap is that? -
我没开玩笑
No, I'm serious.
监视者不知从何处冒出来
I mean, The Monitor shows up here out of nowhere
说你要在12月10日死去
and says that you're supposed to die on December 10th?
我记得上次的报道说
The last I remember, that article said
你在和斯旺大战
that you were in a fight with Thawne,
而不是什么宇宙大灾难
not some cosmic disaster.
-报道变了  -如果那篇报道变了
- The article changed. - If that article can change,
说明我们仍然能够改变未来
then that means that we can still change the future.
那么我们首先应该做什么
So what do we do first?
如果一个医生说你要死了
If a doctor told you you were dying,
你会再去问问其他医生的意见
you'd get a second opinion.
所以我要亲自去看看这个危机
So I'm gonna go see this Crisis for myself.
闪 电 侠
第六季
第二集
你带现金了吗
You bring the cash?
我以为盖特会来
I thought Gat would be here.
盖特没空
Gat's busy.
计划有变
Change of plans.
现在要五千美金
It's $5,000 now.
盖特说的是五百美金
Gat said it was $500.
等等  拜托了  我会拿给你剩下的钱
Okay, wait, please. I will get you the rest.
这事生死攸关
It's a matter of life and death.
求你了  我会给你剩下的钱
Please, I will get the rest of the money.
-我保证  -太迟了
- I promise. - Too late.
大伙  倒计时30秒
T-minus 30 seconds, people.
我就知道这不是个好主意
I knew this was a bad idea.
这是你的主意
This was your idea.
我只是帮你实现
I'm just the guy making dreams come true.
还有20秒
20 seconds, people.
好吧
Okay, fine.
动手吧
Just do it.
起效了吗  我听起来像凯特琳
Did it work? I sound like Caity.
你听着像个普通人  多亏了雷·帕尔默
You sound like a non-meta, thanks to Ray Palmer.
只要这个纳米机器人伪装药剂起效
As long as this nanite camouflage cocktail is active,
你的声音和眼睛
your voice and eyes will allow you to blend in
就能融入普通人群
with any group of regular Joes,
这样你就不用把人们吓个半死
so you can, you know, live your life
过上普通人的生活
without scaring the ever-loving crap out of people.
那我的头发怎么办
And what about my hair?
相信我  你肯定能融入
Trust me. You'll fit right in.
欢迎
Welcome.
你俩别惹祸
Now, you two behave.
我去找我们的明星馆长
I'm gonna go find our star curator.
这些都是什么
What am I looking at here?
你的下一堂课  冰霜
Your next lesson, Frosty.
让我们生活地有价值的东西
Some of the very stuff that makes life worth living:
艺术
art.
我的天哪
Wowsers.
这不是摄影大师卡米拉·王的作品吗
Is this photographer extraordinaire Kamilla Wang?
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
必须的
Yeah, of course.
你的衣服很有品位
Mm, very classy shirt, by the way.
一位非常美丽的摄影师送我的
Oh, a very cute photographer got it for me.
你和她很像呢
She looks a lot like you, actually.
我希望她不介意
I hope she doesn't mind
你已经把衣服弄脏了
that you already got some schmutz on it.
我才没把衣服弄脏
I did not get schmutz--oh.
好吧  我确实弄脏了
Yeah. Yeah, I definitely did.
有时候你希望女朋友的展览
You know, sometimes you just want your girlfriend
成功举办
to have a good turnout for her show,
你让所有人都衣着光鲜
so you make everybody clean up,
结果自己却弄了纳米机器人药剂在衣服上
and who ends up with nanite juice on their shirt?
等等  你带谁来了
Wait, who'd you bring?
你确实非常融入这里
You really do blend in here.
可是这地方太差劲了
Except this place is so lame.
你看看
I mean, come on.
这不是艺术  是垃圾
This isn't art. It's garbage.
别这样冰霜  不是都那样糟糕
Come on, Frost. It's not all that bad.
这些是用过的纸巾
There are used tissues on this.
这就是个马桶搋
Okay? And this is just a plunger.
我的天  快来看看这幅画的笔触
Oh, my God, look at the brushstrokes on this one.
简直...
All right...
不管是谁画的  他一定有问题
Whatever guy made this has some real issues.
好吧冰霜  不过这正是绘画的意义所在
Right, but, Frost, that's kind of the whole point.
艺术可以表达出我们的感受
Art reflects how we feel,
对绘画的感悟
so connecting to art can help us
可以帮助我们发掘更深处的灵魂
plumb the depths of our soul.
好吧
Okay.
我对这些照片的感悟就是
What I am connecting to in these photos
摄影者根本不会聚焦
is that the photographer is afraid to get a shot in focus.
这些其实是我拍的
Those are actually mine.
真是不敢恭维
They're not all winners.
虽然我不介意
Look, I can take a note,
但如果凯特琳的另一面是这样
but if this is how Caitlin's other half is gonna act,
那我下个影展她还是别来了
maybe she should skip my next show.
谢谢你帮我调查这个案子
Thank you for walking me through this one, babe.
不客气  嫌疑人叫阿莱格拉·加西娅
No problem. The suspect is Allegra Garcia.
今年二十岁
She's 20 years old.
她在楔石城郊卖劫车用具
She runs a carjacking outfit out of Keystone.
她的超能力是控制无线电波
Thanks to her meta-human ability to control radio waves.
倒是头一次听说  这可能吗
That's a new one. How is that possible?
车钥匙就是通过无线电来遥控车辆
Key fobs run on radio transmissions.
加西娅从13岁开始
Anyway, Garcia has been in and out of Iron Heights
就是铁山监狱和少管所的常客
and juvie since she was 13.
上周  她企图劫持一个叫
Last week, she tried to hijack a car
萨尔瓦多·特拉弗索的人的车
that belonged to some guy named Salvador Traversoni.
他的车失控了
He lost control of the car,
如你所见  他死于车祸
and, as you can see, he died in the crash.
上面说当时有人看见加西娅在场
It says here an eyewitness puts Garcia
结论显而易见
at the scene, so open and shut.
有你在当然简单了
Should be with you working on it.
击掌
High five.
法官大人  根据所掌握的证据
Your Honor, due to a preponderance of the evidence,
控方主张给予被告人阿莱格拉·加西娅
the State intends to seek the maximum penalty
最高刑罚
against the defendant, Allegra Garcia.
所以我们打算做认罪协商
Which is why the defense would like to plead out.
我的当事人知道陪审团会判处她终身监禁
My client is aware that a jury would put her away for life
所以愿意接受15年左右的刑罚
and is willing to settle for, say, 15 years?
是这样吗  加西娅小姐
Is that true, Ms. Garcia?
-是吧  -好的
- I suppose. - All right, then.
那就不用麻烦陪审团了
I guess we can save the taxpayers some time.
霍尔顿女士
Ms. Horton?
你有什么可看的
What the hell are you staring at?
没什么
Nothing.
只是...
Just, um...
法官大人  控方请求保释加西娅小姐
Your Honor, the prosecution requests bail for Ms. Garcia.
什么
What?
被告人已经认罪了
The defendant is pleading guilty.
是的法官  尽管不合规矩
I know, Your Honor, that it's a bit unorthodox,
但是...
but...
我们发现了一些新证据
we've discovered new evidence.
我们没发现任何新的证据
My office doesn't have the resources to find anything.
我们需要些时间
We just need a little bit of time to determine
来决定是否可以减刑
if the State wants to pursue a lighter sentence.
同时我们请求
In the meantime, we request
在我们继续调查期间
that meta-human dampeners be placed on Ms. Garcia
加西娅小姐需要佩戴阻尼器
while we continue discovery.
霍尔顿律师
Counselor Horton,
本庭赞赏你致力于公正的审判
this court appreciates your commitment to fair jurisprudence,
但是你确定要这样做吗
but are you sure you want to go down this road?
确定  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
是的
Yeah.
你要去哪里
Where will you go?
2019年12月11日
December 11, 2019.
我"消失"的第二天
It's the day after I'm supposed to disappear.
我们应该告诉所有闪电侠小队的人
Maybe we should loop in the rest of Team Flash.
搞清楚真相之前还不行
Not until we know the truth.
我只是不想让你一个人过去
I just--I don't feel great about you going in there alone.
我不是一个人
I'm not gonna be alone.
我有这个
I have this.
你好  巴里·艾伦
Hello, Barry Allen.
启动时间探测程序
Preparing for temporal observational protocol.
这是吉迪恩吗
Is that Gideon?
这是我用基座的废弃零件
It's a mobile Gideon unit I built
制作的便携吉迪恩
from salvaged parts of the plinth.
你会回到现在吧
You'll come right back to this moment?
此时此刻
Right to this second?
我保证
I promise.
即将到达1马赫
Approaching Mach 1.
2马赫
Mach 2.
即将到达2019年11月30日
Now approaching November 30, 2019.
2019年12月1日
December 1, 2019.
检测到障碍
Disruption barrier detected.
什么情况
What the hell?
你的伤口还是没有愈合
Your wound is still not healing.
数据显示你接触到了一种
My readings indicate you were exposed
超自然物质
to an extra-universal material that destroys
物质与其接触时会受到损害
positive matter on contact,
这种物质称为反物质
a substance known as antimatter.
反物质  没听说过
Antimatter? That's new.
就是这种物质阻断了神速力
There's a wall of this stuff clogging up the Speed Force.
吉迪恩  我该怎么通过
Gideon, how do I get past it?
必须寻求外援
Not without additional assistance.
幸而有一位该领域的专家
Fortunately, there is an expert in the field,
杰伊·加里克博士
Dr. Jay Garrick,
也就是地球三的闪电侠
formerly known as the Flash of Earth-3.
地球三
很高兴再次见到你  巴里
Good to see you again, Barry.
我也是 杰伊
You too, Jay.
你是对的
You were right.
你被一记反物质击中了
You were hit with a dose of pure antimatter.
幸运的是你有快速恢复
Lucky you have speed healing,
不然那个擦伤会让你灰飞烟灭
or that scratch could've wiped you out of existence.
有什么办法能让我用穿过那壁垒吗
So is there a way that I can time travel past the barrier?
你能告诉我你最初
You want to tell me why the hell
为什么要穿越时间吗
you were time traveling to begin with?
我需要亲自确认下监视者
I needed to see for myself if The Monitor
说的关于我的未来是否属实
was telling the truth about what happened to me,
我也知道你对穿越时间是什么看法
and I know what you're gonna say about time traveling.
其实  我正准备告诉你
Actually, I was gonna tell you
你做了正确的决定
you made the right call.
过去这一年
For the past year...
我一直监测到反物质信号
I've been detecting antimatter signatures
遍布了多元宇宙
across the Multiverse.
我们不知道它们的来源
Now, we don't know their origin,
但如果我的计算是对的
but if my algorithm is correct,
所有地球都可能处于危险之中
all Earths could be in danger.
那我们得想办法打破那面墙
Then we have to find a way to break through that wall.
用你的身体绝不可能
Ah, your body never could.
但你的思想可能有机会
But maybe your mind can.
我多年前制造了这个东西
I built this thing years ago,
神经超载对撞机
the neural hyper-collider.
它可以收集神经系统电流并经过
It harnesses neural electricity and transfers it
超光速粒子进行传送
across superluminal particles.
因此也就能投射人类意识
Therefore projecting human consciousness
穿越时间与空间
across space-time.
你可以将人的意识送过反物质墙
You could send someone's mind past the antimatter wall.
不是任何人的
Not just anyone.
必须是个极速者
It's gotta be a speedster...
在巅峰时期的
in his prime.
-你行吗  -行
- You in? - Yeah.
那咱们快开始吧
Then let's hustle.
我已经推延晚餐计划了
I've already had to postpone my dinner plans.
希望不会太晚
Not any further, I hope.
妈妈
Mom?
巴里  这是我的妻子
Barry, I'd like you to meet my wife,
琼·威廉姆斯博士
Dr. Joan Williams.
很高兴见到你  巴里·艾伦
It is a pleasure to meet you, Barry Allen.
我听说了你很多事
I've heard quite a bit about you.
阿莱格拉·加西娅
Allegra Garcia.
来自犯罪家庭的少年犯
Juvie offender from a criminal family,
一生都是司法系统的常客
in and out of the system her entire life.
在粒子加速器爆炸那晚
The night of the particle accelerator explosion,
阿莱格拉卷入了一场打斗
Allegra was caught up in a fight.
接下来  她就获得了能够
Next thing you know, she's got the power
控制无线电波的能力
to control radio waves.
然后她被送到了铁山监狱的
Then she gets transferred to the meta-human unit
超能力者牢房
at Iron Heights.
在15岁的时候
At 15?
不算是司法系统最健全的时候
Not exactly the justice system's finest moment.
然后就是现在了
Now here we are.
阿莱格拉再次被逮  但我的能力告诉我
Allegra gets arrested again, but my powers are telling me
这一次她是无辜的
that this time, she's innocent.
但是被害人是被无线电波杀害的
But the victim was killed by a radio wave attack,
也就是阿莱格拉的超能力
which is Allegra's meta-ability.
还有证人证明她在现场
And an eyewitness placed her at the scene.
甚至还认出了她的纹身
Even recognized her tattoo.
我的能力之前从没出过错
My powers have never been wrong before,
我不想让这孩子因为
and I do not want this kid going down
某件她没做的事受牵连
for something she didn't do.
对对对  她没罪
Yeah, yeah, yeah. She's not guilty.
老弟  你干什么  那是我的
Dude, come on. Those are mine.
抱歉  我错了
Sorry. My bad.
看到被害者身上这些烧伤了吗
See these burn marks on the vic?
它们与一般的车辆爆炸不符
They don't match a typical car explosion at all.
就好像是在车祸之前被烧上去的
It's like he was burnt and toasty before the car crash.
我们知道阿莱格拉的能力可以让她
We know that Allegra's powers give her the ability
控制无线电波而不是热浪  所以
to control radio waves and not heat waves, so...
这可能不是阿莱格拉做的
Allegra might not have done this.
我告诉了汉克森法官
And I told Judge Hankerson
阿莱格拉案子有了新证据
there was new evidence in Allegra's case.
好了  现在我们只需要去找出来了
Okay, guys. All we have to do is find it.
中城警局已经审过这个人了
CCPD already interviewed this guy.
你真的认为目击证人会撤回证言吗
You really think the eyewitness is gonna recant his story?
目击证人的证言不总是完美的
Well, eyewitness testimony isn't always perfect.
再说  环境影响  压力
Plus, environmental factors, stress,
甚至是照片的排序都能影响记忆
even the order of lineup photos can effect memory.
所以让他在家里放松状态下回忆
So jogging his memory while he is at home, relaxed
或许能有新进展
might bring something up.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
37号  是这里了
Unit 37. Here it is.
我总是准备充足
I always come prepared.
天啊
Oh, boy.
阿莱格拉
Allegra?
你哪也去不了  好吗
You're not going anywhere, okay?
我们只想和你谈一下
We just want to talk for a second.
不许动  不许动
Freeze! Freeze!
阿莱格拉·加西娅
Allegra Garcia?
你因为违反假释条令被逮捕了
You're under arrest for parole violation.
是我就不会碰
I wouldn't touch that.
抱歉
Sorry.
杰伊告诉我他是你
Jay told me he's a doppelganger
死去父亲的二重身
of your late father.
我有让你联想到你地球上的谁吗
Do I remind you of anyone from your Earth?
有的
Yeah, you do.
她是谁
Who is she?
某个非常特别的人
Someone very special.
是吗
Ain't she?
我从没想到过我会安稳下来
I never thought I'd settle down.
但我需要一个神经学专家来帮助我
But I needed a neurological specialist to help
对抗逐渐失去的速度
with my depleting speed,
然后我们就产生了感情
and something just felt right between us.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
-好了  -那好  来吧
- Yeah. - All right. Come on.
我们开始吧
Let's do it.
杰伊的头盔会帮助你引导超光粒子
Jay's helmet will help channel the tachyons
进入你的额叶皮层
into your frontal cortex
并且点燃你的突触通道
and ignite your synaptic pathways.
说实话  小子
I won't lie to you, kid.
把你的神智发射出反物质墙  是有风险的
Beaming your mind past an antimatter wall...is risky.
我知道
I know.
但是现在是生死攸关的时刻
But right now, it's a matter of life and death.
开始吧
Let's do it.
好吧
All right.
他的生物特征在急速下降
His biometrics are crashing.
我同时收到了时间能量的读数
I'm also picking up temporal energy readings.
他的意识已经冲破了屏障
His mind has broken past the barrier.
他不止找到了一条新的时间线
It's not just a new timeline he's found.
他找到了几十亿个
It's billions of them.
而且巴里正在经历所有的时间线
And Barry's mind is experiencing them all.
为了让几十亿人在这次危机中存活
In order for billions to survive this coming crisis,
闪电侠必须死
the Flash must die.
你赶快把他从那里拉出来
You have to get him out of there.
"为何凡人的灵魂充满荣耀
"Oh, why should the spirit of mortal be proud?
像一闪而过的陨石
"Like a fast-flittering meteor,
翱翔的云朵
"A fast-flying cloud...
一瞬闪电
"A flash of the lightnig...
破灭的浪潮
"A break of the wave...
他的生命消逝  坟墓中安息"
he passes from life to his rest in the grave."
巴里
Barry.
我们在这
You're with us.
威廉·诺克斯
William Knox.
我发现诗歌可以激发
I've discovered that poetry can stimulate
衰退的神经通道
collapsed neural pathways.
对我来说嘎嘎的歌就可以
Lady Gaga usually works for me.
我怎么了
What's wrong with me?
那个设备让你的神经突触过载
The device overloaded your neural synapses,
差一点导致衰竭
creating a near shutdown.
你所感受到的叫做神经熵
What you're experiencing now is called neural entropy.
感觉就像我的神经在着火
It feels like my nerves are on fire.
是的  因为你是一个极速者
They are. Because you're a speedster,
你突触的释放量是正常的十倍
your synapses fire ten times the normal rate,
所以你正在感受一个非极速者
so you're feeling ten times the amount of pain
十倍的痛苦
a non-speedster would.
你过一两天会感觉好一点
You'll feel better in a day or two.
好吧
Okay, okay.
你在那里都看到了什么  小子
What'd you see in there, kid?
我看到
I saw...
几十亿个可能的未来
Billions of possible futures.
几十亿个死亡
Billions of deaths.
他们所有的痛苦和折磨
All their pain, their suffering.
然后他们都死了
And then they were gone.
我感受到了这一切
I felt all of it.
现在我知道监视者说的没错
Now I know the Monitor was right.
我必须死
I have to die.
我需要回家
I need to go home.
巴里  巴里  你现在还不能动
Barry, Barry, you can't be moving.
求你了  我必须要见爱瑞丝
Please, I have to see Iris.
-这样我还是会很痛  -我不明白
- It's not getting any less ow. - I don't understand.
我以为阿莱格拉控制的是无线电波
I thought Allegra controlled radio waves.
我们也以为  但是她释放了一个热浪
So did we, but she fired a heat blast
直冲拉尔夫
right at Ralph.
那不只是热
It wasn't just heat.
那是紫外线辐射
It was ultraviolet radiation.
他晒伤了
He got a sunburn.
是啊  从地狱来的太阳
Yeah. From hell.
看看他的脸
Look at his face.
大部分紫外线都被臭氧层吸收了
Most UV light gets absorbed by the ozone layer.
这一点都没稀释
This was entirely undiluted.
如果不是他有能力的话
If it wasn't for his powers,
那个"晒伤"能杀死他
that "Sunburn" would've killed him.
那敷点芦荟就好了
So put some aloe on it.
好吧
Okay.
我能不能跟凯特琳说两句
Can I just talk to Caitlin for a minute, please?
不行  我还有事要做呢
No. I've got things to do.
我们拿这怎么办
What are we gonna do about this?
别让我开始
Don't even get me started.
听一下  尽管紫外线的波长
Listen, even though UV rays have shorter wavelengths
比无线电波短  但是它们都属于
than radio waves, they're all part of the same
同一种电磁频谱
electromagnetic spectrum.
所以阿莱格拉肯定能控制
So Allegra must be able to control
所有不同的波长
all the different types of wavelengths,
也就意味着她能杀掉萨尔瓦多
which means she could have killed Salvador
还有我们的目击者
and our eyewitness.
然后我放走了她
And I set her free.
来帮我理解一下
Okay, help me understand
你为什么今天早上承认有罪
why you pleaded guilty this morning
然后现在突然就无辜了
and now you're suddenly innocent.
一个女生是可以改变主意的
A girl can change her mind.
你在证人的公寓里做什么
What were you doing at the witness' apartment?
我就是想跟他挑明白
Just needed to hash it out with him,
证明我不是他看见的那个人
prove it was wasn't me he saw.
那是一个警探该干的事
That's something a detective would do.
我想成为一个记者  好吧
I'm trying to be a reporter, okay?
以为这是一个绝好的机会去长点经验
Figured this was as good a time as any to get some experience.
拿到一个报道的同时获得自由
Get a story and my freedom.
但那又有什么用呢
But what's the use?
你还是会认为我是一个罪犯
You'll always see me as a criminal anyway.
你知道我看见什么了吗
You know what I see?
我看见了一个在13岁的时候
I see that scared little kid
抢劫酒品店
that I used to pick up
被我接走的害怕的小孩
for robbing liquor stores when she was 13.
同一个小女孩在我去少管所查看她的时候
That same girl that I would check on in juvie
总是叫我走开
who would always tell me to leave.
今天早上  我收到了一个新号
This morning, I get a ping
你解开了你的超能力者手铐
that you'd escaped from your meta-cuffs,
我们发现你在被害目击证人的家里
and we find you in the location of the dead State's witness.
如果你是记者  你觉得事情会怎样发展
If you're a reporter, how does this story play out?
我没杀他  也没杀那个司机
I didn't kill him or the driver.
我想找出是谁杀了他们  我发誓
I was trying to find out who did it. I swear.
霍尔顿地检官
DA Horton.
我给了你机会  阿莱格拉
I took a chance on you, Allegra.
所以你现在告诉我
So you tell me right now.
到底是谁干的
Who really did it?
告诉我是谁杀了这些人
Tell me who killed those people.
反正你也不会相信我
You wouldn't believe me either.
我想见律师
I want my lawyer.
简直是疯了  简直是疯了
This is insane. This is insane.
所有的证据都表明她有罪
All of the evidence says that she's guilty,
但是
but...
我的超能力告诉我她不仅是无辜的
my powers are telling me that she's not just innocent.
她还知道真正的凶手是谁
She knows who the real killer is.
我只需要她相信我
I just need her to trust me.
你现在需要的是慢下来
All you need to do right now is slow down.
不  我需要做的是找到证据
No, what I need to do is find evidence
在审判之前证明她无罪
to exonerate her before the trial,
而且我快要没时间了
and I am running out of time.
这是因为你想要做
Well, that's because you're trying to do
公设辩护律师的工作  而不是你自己的
the public defender's work and not your own.
你确实知道自己会卷入什么样的麻烦  是吧
You do realize how much trouble you can get in, right?
你出于某种无法解释的原因把阿莱格拉放了
You let Allegra out of jail for an inexplicable reason,
现在又出现了另一起命案
and now there's another murder.
但是我的超能力告诉我
But my powers are telling me--
两个人死了  塞西尔
Two people are dead, Cecile.
你认识这个孩子
You know this kid.
你知道她的犯罪记录  都是抢劫这种轻罪
You know her rap sheet. It's petty crimes, robberies.
不是双重谋杀案  这说不通
It's not double homicide. That doesn't even add up.
我认不出这个女人有段时间了
I haven't known this woman in a long time,
而且证据确凿
and the evidence adds up.
我们要认清  不同于事实的是
We need to recognize that unlike facts,
感觉是不可靠的
feelings can be fallible.
除非这是你的直觉
Except when it's your gut.
-我从来没这样说过  -你不需要这样说
- I've never said that. - You didn't have to.
那是一个吓坏了的孩子
That is a scared kid
没有人为她说话
with no one to stand up for her.
公设辩护律师工作室事务繁忙  工资还很低
The Public Defender's Office is overworked and underpaid.
乔
Joe...
我是唯一能够证明她无辜的人
I'm the only one who can prove her innocence.
你的工作是根据证据
Your job is to prosecute the cases
对你经手的案件
that we bring to you
提起公诉
using the evidence.
我的意思是  就好像
I mean, it's like you...
好像你不想做地检官
it's like you don't even want to be the DA.
你是在告诉我  我必须在
Are you telling me I have to choose
利用能力和做好工作之间做出选择吗
between using my powers and doing my job?
我不是这个意思
That is not what I just said.
不
No.
你就是这样想的
It's what you're feeling.
把他转移到这里来很冒险
It was risky to move him here,
但是他需要见你
but he needed to see you...
我们理解这一点
which we understand.
是的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
我第一次见到你丈夫时  他就那样看着我
Your husband stared at me that same way when we first met.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你和巴里的妈妈长得一模一样
You look just like Barry's mother.
什么
What?
巴里生理上的痛苦会痊愈
Well, Barry's physical pain will go away,
但是心理上
but the mental aspect...
有些创伤不会在短时间内消失
some of that won't, not for a while.
但是我知道你会照顾好他的
But I know you'll keep an eye on him.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们要扫描我们的地球
So they are going to scan our Earth
找出其它反物质迹象
for any other signs of antimatter
并找到方法阻止即将到来的危机
and figure out a way to prevent whatever Crisis is coming.
这并不简单
It's not that simple.
你说你看见一波反物质摧毁了地球
Well, you said you saw a wave of antimatter destroy Earth.
我们需要做的就是制定计划并阻止它
All we have to do is come up with a plan to stop it.
我们无法阻止将要发生的事
We can't stop what's coming.
监视者说的是事实
The Monitor was telling the truth.
我们有卡拉  奥利弗  和其他人
We get Kara and Oliver and everybody.
我们制造一个反物质抑制器
We create an antimatter dampener.
我不在乎  我们只需要找出方法
I don't care. We just find a way.
我看到你  还有凯特琳
I saw you and... Caitlin.
我看到大家都死了
I saw everyone die.
唯一你们都活下来的时间线  就是我死了
The only timeline where you all survived was if I died.
不  不  这不是未来
No, no, that's not the future.
我看到了十亿种未来  爱瑞丝
I saw a billion futures, Iris.
好吧  那第十亿零一种或者第十亿零二种呢
Okay, well, what about the billion and first or billion and second?
我们要掌控自己的命运
We control our destiny.
我们
We...
可以改变出一条更好的时间线
can change the timeline for the better.
也许这就是我被赋予超能力的原因
Maybe this is the reason I was given powers.
为了拯救每一个人
To save everyone.
你今天早上说你还没有放弃
You said this morning that you weren't giving up yet.
我必须接受这一点
I have to accept this.
我们两个都是
We both do.
在你坐在这里等死的时候什么也不要做
And do nothing while you sit here and wait to die?
这不是你的作风
This is isn't you.
我认识的巴里永远不会停止奔跑
The Barry I know would never stop running.
他会找到另一种斗争的方式
He would find another way to fight.
门没锁
It's open.
爱瑞丝不接电话
Iris wasn't answering her phone.
她在这里吗
Is she here?
没有  她在工作
No, no, she's at work.
她在工作
She's working.
你在家里干什么  你还好吗
What are you doing home? You okay?
我在神速力实验时受伤了
I got hurt running a Speed Force experiment,
但我会没事的
but I'll be fine.
好吧
Okay.
如果你有什么事需要爱瑞丝帮忙
If you needed help with something from Iris,
或许我也可以帮你
maybe I could help you out.
是这个案子
It's this case.
阿莱格拉·加西娅
Allegra Garcia.
塞西尔对这个案子很投入
Cecile has some very strong feelings about it.
让我看看
Let me take a look?
你怎么受伤的  巴仔
How did you get hurt, Barr?
好吧  听着
All right, look...
如果你现在不想说就别说
you don't have to share right now if you don't want to.
只要知道我在你身边就好
Just know that I'm here.
一直都在
Always.
有大事要发生了  乔
Something's coming, Joe.
我必须要做出牺牲
I have to make a sacrifice.
但与此同时  我忍不住觉得
But at the same time, I can't help but feeling like
这意味着我就要放弃了
it means I'm giving up.
放弃
Giving up?
是的
Yeah.
当我还是个巡警的时候
When I was a beat cop,
我每天都在同一路线巡逻
you know, I walked the same patrol every day.
有一天早上  我正在处理一起噪音投诉
One morning, I'm responding to a noise complaint.
不知什么地方响起了枪声
Out of nowhere, pop.
子弹掠过我的头顶
Bullet flies by my head.
我趴在地上  我请求了支援  但是
I got pinned down. I called for backup, but...
当时的一切都在告诉我
everything was telling me...
我要死了
that's it.
第二天早上
Next morning...
巴仔  我甚至无法用语言形容
Barr, I can't even tell you how...
我当时有多害怕
scared I was...
回到那些街道上
to go back out in them streets.
但你做到了
But you did.
是的
Yeah.
因为这个
'Cause of this.
中城警局  队长
编号5936
我们的警徽
Our badges,
你的标志  象征着我们的力量
your emblem, they're symbols of the strength
支撑我们回到岗位上
that we're charged with to get back out there.
我们没有选择死亡
And we don't make the choice to die.
我们绝不会选择死亡
We would never choose to do that.
但当我们听到使命的召唤时
But when we hear the call of duty...
我们甘愿做出那样的牺牲
we're willing to make that sacrifice.
那并不是放弃  巴仔
And that's not giving up, Barr.
那被称作顺应力
That's what you call resilience.
我知道你具备那样的品质
And I know you to have plenty of that.
小冰霜
Hey, Frosty.
地球呼叫小冰霜
Earth to Frosty!
异鬼集结
Calling all White Walkers!
好了  别听了
You know what? Frak it.
我在听呢
Hey! I was listening to that.
或许你应该在监听
Maybe you should be listening to
切斯特的分子监控系统
Chester's molecular monitoring system
那样他就不会变回黑洞了
so he doesn't, you know, turn back into a black hole!
放轻松  行吗
Relax, okay?
我把异常警报提醒安装在手机里了
I put the freaking alerts on my phone.
你是说这些异常警报吗
Oh, you mean these freaking alerts?
听着  是我处理了紧急情况
Yeah, see, I handled the situation
防止我们被巨大的真空体
and prevented us from being sucked out of existence
吸入毁灭
by a giant death vacuum.
你周二做了什么
What did you do with your Tuesday?
什么也没做
Nothing.
-那是  -不是  不是
- Is that... - Nope, nope.
不  不  住手  住手
No, no, no, no, no, stop it, stop it.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
你一直在画画吗
Were you drawing?
没有
No.
-你在画画  -没有
- You were drawing. - No.
因为画画是傻瓜才干的事
Because drawing is for losers.
你看起来就是在画画
Looks like you were drawing.
这真的很难  好吗
It's really hard, okay?
这给我的感觉像极简艺术还原论
This is giving me, like, minimalist reductionism.
我是想画这个
I was trying to draw this.
我画了好久
I've been working on it forever.
还是一点进展也没有
And it's not getting any better.
行了  那是
All right, that's...
这就是你自从看完卡米拉的画展后
Is this why you've been all cranky pants
一直这么暴躁的原因吗
since Kamilla's show?
你只是想表达自己的看法
You've just been trying to express yourself.
我惹人嫌  行了吧
I stink, okay?
我不知为何想要探寻自己的灵魂深处
I don't know why I thought I could plumb the depths of my soul.
你不惹人嫌
You do not stink.
你想成为文森特·梵·斯诺
You want to go off and be Vincent van Snow?
你想用艺术  绘画或舞蹈展示你的内心世界
You want to show the world what's inside of you
那就去做吧
using art or paint or dance, do it.
但你要明白
But you gotta understand that...
别人也在尝试这样做
other people are trying to do it too.
我感觉像在被黑社会捅腹一样
I feel like a Yakuza baddie is stabbing me in the stomach.
反反复复
Repeatedly.
这就是我在卡米拉的画展上给大家的感受吗
Is this how I made everyone feel at Kamilla's show?
没错  这就是所谓的愧疚感
Yep. That's a feeling we like to call guilt.
有点小疼  但是
It's a little stabby. But...
它也能告诉我们什么时候应该做出改正
it can also show us when we need to make something right.
我说过了  我要见我的律师
I told you, I want my lawyer.
史蒂文还在路上
Steven's still on his way.
听着  我理解你现在的感受
Look, I understand what you're going through.
你知道没有这双手铐时我会看到什么吗
Do you know what I see when these cuffs are off?
我看到无线电波和微波
I see radio waves and microwaves
还有伽马波
and gamma waves,
而我无法无视它们的存在
and I can't stop seeing them.
所以你怎么可能理解我现在的感受
So how could you possibly understand what I'm going through?
你得让我帮你
You have to let me help you.
-好让你判我刑  -不  这不是我来此的原因
- So you can put me away? - No, that's not why I'm here.
那你为什么来
Then why are you?
因为
Because I...
因为我也是超能力者
Because I am a meta-human too.
我可以感受到别人的情感
I can sense other people's feelings,
而且亲爱的  我也没法关掉它
and, honey, I can't turn it off either.
这就是为什么我知道你是无辜的
That's how I know that you're innocent.
如果有什么能让我说服其他人
If there is anything that can help me convince everybody else...
求你
please...
你定要告诉我
you gotta tell me.
我跟逮捕我的警官说了
I told my arresting officer.
他说我疯了
He said I was crazy.
我也感觉疯了
I feel crazy.
试试我
Try me.
在少管所时
Back at juvie...
粒子加速器爆炸那晚
the night that particle accelerator exploded,
我不是一个人
I wasn't alone.
我的表姐也在那里
My cousin was there at the same time.
伊丝丽兰萨
Esperanza.
谈起坏影响
Talk about bad influences.
我想要退出她的帮派  所以她偷袭了我
I wanted out of her gang, so she jumped me.
她在爆炸中死了
She died in the explosion.
伊丝丽兰萨
Esperanza!
至少我是这么认为的
Or at least I thought she did.
你认为她还活着吗
You think she's still alive?
伊丝丽兰萨逼我弄了和她一样的纹身
Esperanza made me get the same tattoo as her.
目击证人就是认出了你那纹身
The witness ID'd you off that tat.
但是伊丝丽兰萨死了
But Esperanza's dead.
不可能是她
There's no way it could be her.
我是说  有可能
I mean, it's impossible.
对吗
Right?
你拿到那少管所记录了吗
Hey, did you get those juvie records?
是的  四处伸缩了下
Oh, yeah. Took a bit of stretching,
我们这里大概有五年的记录
but we got about five years' worth here.
好  有没有伊丝丽兰萨·加西娅的记录
Good. Is there a file on a girl named Esperanza Garcia?
有  在这里
Yeah, there is.
我闻到了谜题
And I smell a mystery.
"犯人被发现处于植物人状态"
"Inmate was discovered in a vegetative state.
"她已经被转移出我监狱"
She has been taken out of our custody."
从监狱转移到一个被描得很黑的组织
Out of custody into the hands of a very redacted organization.
伊丝丽兰萨还活着
Esperanza's alive.
塞西尔  你听到了吗
Cecile, did you hear that?
塞西尔  你得去...
Cecile, you got--get--there.
那不是我
That's not me.
给我阿莱格拉·加西娅
Bring me Allegra Garcia...
不然就烧死
or burn.
我们得带你出去
We gotta get you out of here.
来吧  快来
Come on. Come on.
滚出我的警局
Get out of my precinct!
该死
Damn it.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
巴里  我们正在和塞西尔谈她的案子
Barry, we were talking to Cecile about her case.
结果发现阿莱格拉有个表姐名叫
Turns out that Allegra had a cousin named
伊丝丽兰萨  有着和她一样的能力
Esperanza with the same powers as her.
所有人都以为伊丝丽兰萨死了
Everybody thought that Esperanza was dead.
肯定是伊丝丽兰萨杀了证人  不是阿莱格拉
Esperanza must've killed the witness, not Allegra.
伊丝丽兰萨不会让任何人知道她还活着
Now Esperanza can't let anyone know she's alive.
中城警局完全被隔断了
CCPD is in a total blackout.
她要去找阿莱格拉
She's going after Allegra.
我现在派拉尔夫赶过去
I am going to send Ralph there right now and--
不不  没时间了  我去吧
No, no, no, there's no time. I'm going.
巴里  不行  你还在恢复
Barry, no. You're still recovering.
我没事的  好吗  我立刻就去
I'll be fine, all right? I'm going.
伊丝丽兰萨
Esperanza.
这不是你
你说得对
伊丝丽兰萨五年前死了
我现在是致命紫光了
I'm only Ultraviolet now.
不  我不会让你这么做的
No! I won't let you do this.
那你也会死
Then you'll die too.
保护好他们
Keep them safe.
起来  英雄
Get up, hero.
我要让你站着迎接死亡
I want you to die on your feet.
刚才怎么回事
How did that happen?
紫外线传播速度是美妙三十万公里
Ultraviolet light travels at 186,000 miles per second,
比你最高速度快30倍
which is 80 times your top speed.
我建议立刻撤退
I suggest a hasty retreat.
真理  自由  正义
我们的警徽  你的标志
Our badges, your emblem...
当我们听到使命的召唤时
when we hear the call of duty...
我们甘愿做出那样的牺牲
we're willing to make that sacrifice.
那并不是放弃  巴仔
And that's not giving up, Barry.
那被称作顺应力
That's what we call resilience.
我知道你具备那样的品质
And I know you to have plenty of that.
好多了
That's better.
塞西尔  叫医生
Cecile, call the medic!
你知道他们说的
You know what they say.
放个几天就有棕皮肤了
In a few days, it'll be tan.
我只庆幸还活着
Yeah, well, I'm just glad to be alive.
我们是对的
We were right.
伊丝丽兰萨·加西娅被雇来
Esperanza Garcia was hired
杀死萨尔瓦多·特拉弗索
to kill Salvador Traversoni.
然后她除掉了目击证人
Then she offed the eyewitness.
她想要杀死阿莱格拉  防止有人知道她还活着
She tried to kill Allegra so nobody would know she was still alive.
你跳过了关于
And you skipped over the part
这位致命紫光可能接受了
where this Ultraviolet person might've been trained
一个秘密组织的刺杀训练
in the art of assassination by a secret organization.
是  这个在我待解决的名单上
Yeah, that's on my to-solve list.
现在是在我们的名单上了
Yeah, well, it's on ours now.
如果有这么个组织在利用超能力者
If there's a group out there exploiting metas,
那么他们需要我们的保护
then they're gonna need our protection.
你给我打了止痛药吗
What'd you put in these painkillers?
你没有出现幻觉
Oh, you're not hallucinating.
这是艺术
That is art.
有些人可能认为它很怪异
And some people might think it's weird.
但我认为它是艺术家内心世界
But I think it is a beautiful expression
美丽的表达
of the artist's inner life.
即使是奇怪的内心世界
Even if it's a weird inner life.
但你买了下全部这些
But you bought all this stuff?
你怎么支付得起
I mean, how'd you pay for it?
刷凯特琳的信用卡  全用了
With Caity's credit cards. All of them.
我们下节人生课程讲讲财务管理吧
Maybe our next life lesson will be in personal finance.
实际上
Actually...
我还有一幅画可以加入它们
I've got one more piece to add to the bunch.
出自一位年轻大胆的天才之手
From a very daring young talent.
它们把房间装饰得相当好看
I think it ties the room together quite nicely.
每个人都有自己的品位
Well, there's no accounting for taste.
我妈妈曾经交往过一个搞艺术的
You know, my mom dated an artist once.
但他是表演空中飞人的
He was a trapeze artist, though.
大家都叫他"没脖子尼克"
No-Net Nick, they called him.
两本故事书  三首摇篮曲
Two books and three bedtime songs...
小詹娜可算睡着了
but little Jenna is finally asleep.
她很坚持不懈
She is persistent.
这是遗传了她妈妈
She gets that from her mother.
你为阿莱格拉挺身而出
Look, you stood up for Allegra...
其他人都没有  包括我
when nobody else did, including myself.
是你勇猛的突袭了一个闪电女杀手
Well, you are the badass that charged a light-wielding hit woman
救了我们的命
in order to save all of our butts.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我不断在想
I just keep thinking.
身为地方检察官  我没能竭尽全力
I'm not doing everything I can to help the city
帮助这座城市
as the district attorney.
司法体系并不完全适用于超能力者
The justice system doesn't always work for metas...
所以我想成为一位
which is why I want to become
超能力者的辩护律师
a defense attorney for meta-humans.
我知道  你可以说我疯了
I know. I know. You can tell me that I'm crazy,
今天阿莱格拉的事我们也有分歧
and we were not on the same page about Allegra today--
不不不  这不是疯了
No, no, no, that's not crazy.
-这很了不起  -真的吗
- That is incredible. - Really?
你知道这样能帮助这座城市多少人吗
Babe, do you know how many people you could help in this city?
没错
Yeah.
而且我知道该从哪开始
And I know right where I want to start.
《中城市民》报
闪电侠打败强力超能力者  拯救中城警局
你好
Um, hi.
我找爱瑞丝·韦斯特艾伦
I'm looking for Iris West-Allen.
我听说你们招实习的
I'm here about the internship.
你好  塞西尔·霍尔顿跟我提到你了
Hi, yeah, Cecile Horton told me to expect you.
欢迎加入《公民报》
Welcome to "The Citizen."
注意不要动我的素食甜甜圈
Just don't touch the vegan doughnuts.
你可以把你的东西放那边
You can put your things right over there.
现在做什么
So what now?
我们继续扫描多元宇宙
We'll keep scanning the Multiverse
寻找我实验室里的反物质
for antimatter from my lab, okay?
但现在我觉得我们该走了
But I think, for now, we should get going.
是的  没错
Yes, we should.
英勇的记者
Ah, the intrepid reporter.
我以为你有报道要发表
I thought you had a story to put out.
我不能让你不辞而别
Well, I couldn't let you leave without saying good-bye.
我知道现在不是最理想的状况
And I know it hasn't been under the best of circumstances,
但我希望还能再见到你们
but I hope we will see you guys again.
-希望如此  -是的
- I hope so. - Yeah.
下次再见  闪电侠
Till next time, Flash.
好的
Yeah.
很高兴认识你  巴里·艾伦
It was a pleasure to meet you, Barry Allen.
继续做好我们心目中的英雄
You keep being the hero we know you are.
我会的
I will.
准备好了
You ready?
好了
Yes.
我知道她不是你妈妈  但...
I know she's not your mom, but...
在糟糕的日子里抱有一点希望也不错
Still nice to have a little hope on a not-so-great day.
是的
Yeah.
之前的事很抱歉
I'm sorry about earlier.
不用抱歉
Don't be.
你很痛苦  很受惊
You were in pain and shock, and...
我也很害怕
I was scared too.
但看到你在中城警局
But seeing you at CCPD,
全力以赴战斗
fighting with your all,
这提醒了我
it reminded me that...
无论这次危机将带来什么
no matter what this Crisis brings...
无论你如何选择
no matter what you choose...
我知道你绝不会放弃
I know that you're never gonna give up.
我不会选择死亡
I'm not choosing to die.
我无法做出离开你的选择
I could never make the choice to leave you.
但是
But...
如果只有我死
if my death is...
才能拯救这个宇宙
the only way to save the universe,
拯救你
to save you...
我愿意那么做
I'm willing to do that.
那...
Then...
无论接下来做什么  我们要做得有意义
whatever we do next, let's make it count.
我们可以从准备让小队迎接这次危机开始
We can start by preparing the team for this Crisis.
甚至一个没有闪电侠的世界
Maybe even a world without the Flash.
那我们怎么和他们说
So what do we tell them?
开始对患者1-A进行活检测试
Beginning biopsy examination on Patient 1-A,
米切·罗密欧  40多岁男性
Mitch Romero, male, 40s.
我希望这次手术
It is my hope that this procedure
可以帮助证明我的治疗效果
will help to illuminate the effects of my cure...
在接触另一项课题时
when exposed to another subject.
身体没有明显出血迹象
The body presents no obvious signs of hemorrhaging.
但看起来受害者的血液
But it appears the victim's blood...
和一种无法辨别的生物物质凝结了
has coagulated with an unidentifiable biological substance.
我要对该物质进行分析
Will run analysis on the substance.
物质在受害者死前可能已经吸收进血管了
Substance could have been absorbed into victim's veins prior death.